atlantis.com 2013-05-01

# Privacy Policy: Atlantis Resort & Casino Paradise Island Bahamas BS

ATLANTIS ONLINE PRIVACY

This is the web site of Atlantis, Paradise Island, Bahamas.  
Owned and operated by Kerzner International Resorts, Inc.   
Our postal address is   
1000 South Pine Island Road   
Plantation, FL 33324  

We are providing you with this Privacy Policy (“Privacy Policy”) because we understand that you are concerned about privacy.  This Privacy Policy pertains to the www.Atlantis.com website (the "Site") operated by Kerzner International Resorts, Inc., on behalf of its affiliated companies and affiliated properties, including Atlantis, Paradise Island, Bahamas (collectively, “us” or “we”).  This Privacy Policy describes how personal information about you may be collected, used and disclosed by us in the course of business.  It also describes how you can opt-out of some uses of personal information. 

This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and is subject to our Terms and Conditions. Your use of our services, including this Site and any personal information you provide us remains subject to the terms of this Privacy Policy and our Terms and Conditions. If you do not agree with this Privacy Policy please do not use this Site.

Please review this Privacy Policy carefully.

The effective date of this Privacy Policy is: September 1, 2008.

INFORMATION WE COLLECT, HOW WE COLLECT IT AND ITS USES

Your personal information and non-personal information may be shared for any purpose among Kerzner International Resorts, Inc and with its affiliated companies and affiliated properties and service providers and contractors for limited purposes, including fulfilling customer reservations; offering certain products and services in connection with our Site; communicating to customers; providing customer service; enhancing and improving customers' online experience; enabling access to our partners' sites; providing a personalized online experience; and completing credit card transactions. Otherwise, except for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy, we do not share your personal information with any other third parties unless we have your permission.   
When using our Site, you may be asked to voluntarily provide certain personal information. You can use our Site without creating an account, but you will need to create an account if you want to take advantage of certain features, such as "MyPlan" and other time saving features. Also, upon your registering at check-in we may request that you provide us certain information in our guest cards or similar registration materials. When you place a reservation or register at check-in, we request your name, email address, mailing address, phone number, credit card number and expiration date. We may also ask for personal information when you contact our reservations department or other customer service departments. This will allow us to assist you better and to protect your confidentiality by verifying your identity.

Your resort stay information is collected and stored by our resort locally, and subsequently transferred to a centralized database in the United States. This facilitates aggregated trend analysis used for resort management purposes such as planning new resort locations, evaluating resort amenities, guest preferences, and advertisement planning. In addition, your business with us is valued and we may use the record of your stay to send you via postal mail or email, communications such as guest surveys or promotional offers and benefits. You may “opt-out” or choose to be excluded from these communications by noting this on your guest registration during your resort stay or by contacting us as provided below in "How To Contact Us." 

Tracking Technology: As a part of our standard data collection process, we collect the e-mail addresses of those who communicate with us via e-mail. We may track your movement within the Site, the pages from which you were referred, access times and browser types. We only use this information in aggregate and do not link it to you personally. To gauge the effectiveness of our Site, we do collect some generic information about our visitors. Our web servers automatically recognize a visitor's domain name, the web page from which a visitor enters our Site, which pages a visitor visits on our Site, and how much time a visitor spends on each page and logs IP addresses. We may use anonymous tracking technologies to collect, store and sometimes track information for statistical purposes and to improve the services we provide. We aggregate this information and use it to evaluate and improve our Site. 

We store information that we collect through cookies, log files, clear gifs, and/or third party sources for instance to verify your address and update your information. A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user's computer for record-keeping purposes. We may use cookies on this Site. We may use session ID cookies and persistent cookies. We use session cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our Site. A session ID cookie expires when you close you browser. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser's "help" file Persistent cookies are used to differentiate subscribers from non-subscribers to customize the content of certain sections of the website and enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our Site. If you reject cookies, you may still use our Site, but your ability to use some areas of our Site, such as promotions or surveys, may be limited. Some of our business partners may use cookies on our Site and we have no access to or control over these cookies. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by us only and does not cover the use of cookies by any such third parties.

We are currently using and have contracted with Omniture, a third party, to track and analyze non-personally identifiable usage and volume statistical information from our visitors and customers to administer our Site and constantly improve its quality. All data collected by Omniture on our behalf is owned and used by us. We reserve the right to publish non-personally identifiable, summary information regarding its Site visitors for promotional purposes and as a representative audience for advertisers. Please note that it is not personal information, only general summaries of the activities of our visitors and customers. For more information about Ominiture's privacy policy, including how to opt out, go to www.omniture.com/policy.html.

Sweepstakes or Promotions: From time to time we may provide you the opportunity to participate in sweepstakes or other promotions on our Site or otherwise, which might be sponsored or conducted by a third party. If you participate, we will request certain personally identifiable information from you such as name, mailing address, zip code and age. Participation in these sweepstakes is completely voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose this information. We may transfer personal information to certain sponsors and ad partners that you have explicitly requested to receive information from.  It will be clear at the point of collection who is collecting the personal information and whose privacy statement will apply.

Some of our promotional offers have a feature that allows you to have the offer sent to a friend with your comment. If you choose to use this feature, we collect the email address of your friend(s) to facilitate the referral.

Surveys: We may from time to time provide a survey for our readers to fill out providing us with demographic information (such as income level and gender) to us. We encourage you to submit this information so we can provide you a more personalized experience on our Site but participation is entirely voluntary. 

Third Party Links: We encourage you to be aware when you leave our Site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This Privacy Policy applies only to information collected by our Site   
Children's Privacy: We respect the privacy of children, and do not collect any more personal information than reasonably necessary to enable them to participate in the activities we offer at our Site. We will not use information collected on our website from children for direct sales solicitations without their parent or guardian’s consent in compliance with applicable law.  
Exceptional Circumstances: If Kerzner International Resorts, Inc., or any of its affiliated companies or properties, is sold or disposed of as a going concern, whether by merger, sale of assets or otherwise, the relevant customer database of Kerzner International Resorts, Inc. could, in whole or in part, be sold as part of that transaction. In the event Kerzner International Resorts, Inc. goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, your personal information will likely be among the assets transferred. We also may have to release personal information when it is necessary to comply with judicial or other government subpoenas, warrants, orders, to enforce our Terms and Conditions or to protect the rights, property, or safety of Kerzner International Resorts, Inc. or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection.

We may use personal information and non-personal information for purposes unrelated to marketing, including: 

(1) responding to your inquiries, complaints and other communications;  
(2) processing and fulfilling reservations and/or purchases and making a record of such reservations and purchases;   
(3) bill your credit card for advance purchase reservations and advance deposits   
(4) contacting you for confirmation or customer service after reservations and purchases are made or after you sign up for or participate in certain activities;   
(5) for statistical or demographic analysis;   
(6) for tracking reservations and corresponding resort stays;   
(7) sending you emails that relate to a resort stay; and   
(8) communicating special offers and featured items to you, if you choose to receive such notices. 

VISITORS OUTSIDE OF THE UNITED STATES

Our Site is maintained on servers located in the United States, and personal information is also stored on computers located in the United States.  The United States may not offer a level of privacy protection for personal information as great as that offered in other jurisdictions.  Therefore, the disclosure of personal information pursuant to this Privacy Policy is at your own risk.  We make no representation that the practices described in this Privacy Policy are compliant with laws outside of the United States that apply to the collection, security, use and disclosure of personal information. 

SECURITY 

We have security procedures in the storage and disclosure of personal information in order to prevent unauthorized access. Keep in mind however, that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.  Our Site may also contain links to other websites.  Keep in mind that we do not control and are not responsible for the privacy or security practices or the content of these or other websites. 

We cannot enforce or control the security of the computers, electronic devices, or electronic communication method that a consumer may utilize to send e-mails and submit information to us over the Internet.  You are responsible for ensuring that the computers, electronic devices and electronic communication methods you utilize will provide adequate security for communicating with us.  We are not responsible for the disclosure or interception of your information before we receive it.

Email Communications

We do not intentionally send you unsolicited email marketing communications. If you choose to receive periodic communications from us, we may from time to time send you email messages describing new promotions, featured resorts and special offers. When you join our email list, we request your email address in order to send you email on the latest offers, advanced notice of events, and more. You can choose to stop receiving these emails at any time. 

If you are no longer interested in receiving our mail communications, instructions for removal from the list are included in the email we send you.

Telemarketing

Although you may have registered your telephone number on a Federal or State do not call list, certain exemptions (for example, for communicating with established customers) may allow us to contact you via telephone. However, to ensure our customer’s preferences are honored, we also maintain our own internal “Do Not Call” list.  If you would like to opt-out of receiving telemarketing sales calls from us regarding new products and services or upcoming events by adding your telephone number to our internal Do Not Call list, please call 1-888-528-7155. 

How do I correct or update my information?

You can modify your personal information anytime. Simply go to"MyPlan", log in and edit whatever information you wish. Please note that we retain your credit card information for a short period after your online reservation or use of the credit card at our properties so we do not retain such information in "MyPlan." If you wish to delete your "MyPlan" profile entirely, please contact us as provided below in "How To Contact Us."

CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

We reserve the right to revise this Privacy Policy at any time without notice.  From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our Privacy Policy. If our information practices change at some time in the future, we will post the Privacy Policy changes to our Site to notify you of these changes and provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses. Any revised Privacy Policy will only apply prospectively to personal information or non-personal information collected or modified after the effective date of the revised policy. You should periodically review the Privacy Policy available at our Site for revisions.  Use of our Site after revision of the Privacy Policy signifies your consent to the revised Privacy Policy.

HOW TO CONTACT US

If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us at our postal address: 

1000 South Pine Island Road   
Plantation, FL 33324 

If you do not want to receive e-mail from us in the future, please let us know by calling us at 1-888-528-7155. If you supply us with your postal address on-line you may receive periodic mailings from us with information on new products and services or upcoming events. If you do not wish to receive such mailings, please let us know by calling us at 1-888-528-7155.  
Upon request we provide Site visitors with access to all information including proprietary information that we maintain about them. Customers can access this information and if errors are found, request that this information be corrected by calling us at 1-888-528-7155.   
If you feel that this Site is not following its stated policy, please contact the Web Administrator at the corporate office by calling 954-809-2000. 

Your California Privacy Rights   
Under California Civil Code sections 1798.83-1798.84, California residents are entitled to ask us for a notice describing what categories of personal customer information we share with third parties or corporate affiliates for those third parties or corporate affiliates' direct marketing purposes. That notice will identify the categories of information shared and will include a list of the third parties and affiliates with which it was shared, along with their names and addresses. If you are a California resident and would like a copy of this notice, please submit a written request to the address as provided above in "How To Contact Us.". In your request, please specify that you want a "Your 's California Privacy Rights Notice". Please allow 30 days for a response.
